Guide to the Benjamin Newton Duke Papers, 1834-1984, bulk 1884-1929.
The Benjamin Newton Duke papers 1834-1984 bulk 1884-1929.
Duke, Benjamin Newton
69 Linear Feet Approximately 50,850 Items
Duke University. David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Durham, North Carolina 27708-0185
Benjamin Newton Duke (1855-1929) was the primary philanthropist in the Duke family and the eldest of Washington Duke's sons. He held a leadership role in several of the family companies, and was instrumental in founding Duke University.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The papers of Benjamin Newton Duke, tobacco manufacturer, industrialist and philanthropist, have been received from a variety of sources over an extended period of time. While acquisition information about the bulk of the collection is unrecorded, it is believed that it was given by his daughter, Mary Duke Biddle. Additions to the collection were made by Mary Duke Biddle, 1939; Alexander H. Sands, Jr., 1940- 1941, 1953; R.D. Graham, 1950; Mrs. Lucy Cole Durham, 1951; Mrs. James H. Semans (Mary Duke Biddle Trent Semans), 1961-1972; Bud Alexander, 1970; Duke University Archives, 1980; and Julia Wightman, 1990.
Biographical Note
1855, Apr. 27 Born to Washington and Artelia Roney Duke; Orange Co., N.C.
1856 Brother, James Buchanan Duke, born
1858 Mother, Artelia Roney Duke, died of typhoid
1871 Enrolled New Garden School (later Guilford College), near Greensboro, N.C.
1874 Father moved family to Durham proper
1877, Feb. 21 Married Sarah Pearson Angier
1878 Duke, Sons and Company established
188?, Oct. 3 Son, George Washington Duke, born. Died at age 2 or 3
1884, Dec. 8 Son, Angier Buchanan Duke, born
1887, Nov. 16 daughter, Mary Lillian Duke, born
1889 Elected member Board of Trustees, Trinity College
1890-? Director, American Tobacco Company
1891 Brought William A. Erwinto Durham. Established Erwin Mills
1893-1922 President, The Fidelity Bank of Durham, N.C.
1898 Delegate, General Conference, Methodist Episcopal Church, South, Baltimore, Md.
1905, June 22 Southern Power Company established by Benjamin N. and James B. Duke, (later Duke Power Company)
1905, May 8 Father, Washington Duke, died
1923, Sept. 3 Son, Angier Buchanan Duke, died
1925, Oct. 10 Brother, James Buchanan Duke, died
1929, Jan. 8 Died New York City. Buried in family mausoleum at Maplewood Cemetery, Durham, N.C.
1936 Remains removed to the Memorial Chapel of Duke University Chapel along with those of father, Washington Duke, and brother, James Buchanan Duke
1936, Sept. 3 Wife, Sarah Pearson Angier Duke, died
Benjamin Newton Duke took a leading role in the development of the tobacco, textile and hydroelectric power industries in North Carolina. He served as president of Citizens National Bank in Durham, N.C., and of the Southern Railway Company. Along with his brother, James Buchanan Duke, and their partner, George Washington Watts, Benjamin Duke held substantial investments in a variety of enterprises throughout the United States.
Benjamin Duke took a primary role in conducting the Duke family's philanthropies from the late 1880s until his death. Between 1892 and 1927 it is estimated he contributed to over 400 organizations or institutions, including churches, hospitals, orphanages, schools and universities. This does not take into account assistance given to relatives and other individuals.
Collection Overview
The papers of Benjamin Newton Duke span the years 1834 to 1984, though the bulk of the papers date from 1884 to 1929. The collection is arranged into seven series: Correspondence; Financial Papers; Legal Papers; Pictures; Richard B. Arrington Papers; Alexander H. Sands, Jr., Papers; and Miscellaneous Papers. The collection reflects the financial, philanthropic, and social interests of Benjamin Newton Duke and his family. Its primary focus is the family's business dealings including their involvement in the development and growth of tobacco manufacturing, textiles, and hydroelectric power in the southern United States. Philanthropic interests are well represented throughout the collection and include education, social welfare, the Methodist Church (South) as well as individuals. Personal and family relationships, though less well-documented, are primarily related to social activities revolving around their homes in Durham, N.C., New York City, and winter trips to Florida. Besides Benjamin Newton Duke, other family members represented in this collection include: James Buchanan Duke, Washington Duke, Sarah Pearson Angier Duke, Angier Buchanan Duke, Mary Duke Biddle, Anthony J. Drexel Biddle, and other Duke, Angier, Biddle, Roney, and Lyons relatives.
The majority of the letters in the Correspondence Series are concerned with business and philanthropic interests. The day-to-day affairs of Mr. Duke and his family were handled through personal secretaries or agents in either the New York or Durham, N.C., business offices, and much of the correspondence reflects this. Over the years these agents included: Richard B. Arrington, Miss E. A. Childs, Alexander H. Sands, Jr., and J.E. Stagg.
Mr. Duke's business interests centered on tobacco manufacturing, banking, textiles, mining, transportation, and hydroelectric power in North Carolina and throughout the United States. His primary business partners were Washington Duke (his father), James Buchanan Duke (his brother), George Washington Watts and William A. Erwin. The major companies represented in the Correspondence Series include: W. Duke, Sons and Company; Allen and Company; American Tobacco Company; British-American Tobacco Company; Liggett and Meyers Tobacco Company; R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company; Citizens National Bank of Durham, N.C.; Bank of Harnett, N.C.; The Fidelity Bank of Durham, N.C.; Guaranty Trust Company of New York; Erwin Cotton Mills; Cannon Manufacturing Company; Mayo Mills; Odell Manufacturing Company; Southern Cotton Oil Company; Durham Fertilizer Company; Jim Butler Tonopah Mining Company; Republic Iron and Steel Company; Seaboard Air Line Railway; Dallas Cable Railroad; Kansas City, Mexico & Orient Railway Company; Durham and Southern Railway Company; Georgia Railway and Power Company; Durham Electric Lighting Company; Spray Water and Power Company; and Southern Power Company (later Duke Power Company). Other investments included real estate, spring and mineral water companies, and the motion picture industry. The latter is represented by letters and minutes (1915) of The National Drama Corporation (founded by Thomas Dixon) to produce a movie entitled Fall of a Nation, a sequel to Birth of a Nation.
Mr. Duke's philanthropic interests were equally as numerous as his business interests. The Correspondence Series reflects his generosity to both black and white institutions and individuals. Major support was given to schools, churches and social welfare agencies. Among those supported were Trinity College (later Duke University), Greensboro Female College, Louisburg Female College, Kittrell College, Elon College, Lincoln Memorial University, North Carolina College for Negroes, The Bingham School,Trinity Church, Main Street Church,West Durham Methodist Church, National Religious Training School and Chatauqua for the Colored Race, Oxford Orphan Asylum, the Salvation Army, the Durham Y.M.C.A. and Y.W.C.A., and Lincoln Hospital.
Personal letters in the Correspondence Series reflect the activities and interests of a socially prominent family during the 19th and early 20th centuries. Also shown is Mr. Duke's support of various relatives over the years. Family members represented include: Benjamin Newton Duke,James Buchanan Duke, Sarah Pearson Angier Duke, Angier Buchanan Duke, Mary Duke Biddle, and Anthony J. Drexel Biddle. Additional letters are from members of the Duke, Angier,Biddle, Roney and Lyons families, as well as a variety of friends, acquaintances and strangers seeking his financial assistance. Among the personal correspondence is a response concerning the Julian Shakespeare Carr/Daniel Lindsey Russell gubernatorial campaign (1896) and a series of letters from son-in-law Anthony J. Drexel Biddle (over Christmas/New Years 1918-1919) concerning demobilization and the League of Nations.
The Financial Papers Series complements information found in the Correspondence Series and pertains to the purchase and sale of stock, household expenses, farm expenditures, bills, Mr. Duke's contributions and gifts, transactions for the purchase and repair of automobiles, and the building and furnishing of Duke homes in New York and North Carolina. This series is also an excellent source for examples of 19th-century advertising artwork. Secretary/agents managed the personal expenses and investment portfolios of Benjamin Newton Duke, Sarah Pearson Angier Duke,Angier Buchanan Duke, and Mary Duke Biddlein addition to Mr. Duke's business and philanthropic affairs as reflected in this series. Household expenses for the Duke homes in New York City and Four Acresin Durham, N.C., as well as upkeep of the Duke Farmin Orange County, N.C., were handled through these agents. Stock transactions were handled through a number of brokers, including: Daniel O'Dell & Company, Dominick & Dominick, Halstead & Hagemeyer, and Moore & Schley.
Topical files in the Financial Papers Series concern stock transactions, personal family accounts and charitable contributions. Early minute books and stock certificates for the Alaska Dredging and Power Company and the Solomon River Hydraulic Mining Company, and the stocks, bonds, and dividend records for the Southern Investment Company of Canada, Ltd., are included in this series. To a lesser degree, the Financial Papers Series deals with business affairs of Washington Duke. A cashbook for W. Duke, Sons and Company (1891) also includes trial balances for both Washington Duke (1893-1897) and Benjamin Duke (1893-1897). Brodie L. Duke's involvement with W. Duke, Sons and Company is shown in an account book pertaining to tobacco purchases (1876-1878) and also in the Correspondence Series (1890s). The interrelationship of the business dealings of Benjamin and James Duke can be found throughout the collection.
Property transactions in Orange County and Durham, N.C.,are found in the Legal Papers Series. Beginning in 1834 the records include deeds and plats and contain the names of early families in Durham. Other records in this series include charters for various businesses; papers regarding the Kimball Town Company, a milltown in Marion County, Tenn. (1890); a legal brief concerning a lawsuit brought by Richard Wrightin 1891; and a copy of Washington Duke's will (1905).
Albums, in the Pictures Series, contain primarily cabinet cards inserted in Victorian binders. Most of these photographs date from the late 1800s and are of Duke family members, including Angier and Lyon relatives. Other persons included are Bishop Charles Betts Galloway, Reverend William S. Black, Arthur H. Merritt, and President and Mrs. Grover Cleveland. In addition to the albums in this series, there are individual photographs of Mary Duke Biddle, Angier Buchanan Duke, Benjamin Newton Duke, Cordelia Biddle Duke, Sarah Pearson Angier Duke and Washington Duke dating from the 1880s to 1920s. Group pictures taken on the boardwalk (1924) in Atlantic City, N.J., also include James Buchanan Duke, Robert Lee Flowers and Lily Parrish Flowers. Other photographs are of Professor Dowd, John Acero Angier, James Haywood Southgate, and Reuben Oscar Everett. Photographs also represent buildings and property. There is a large group of photographs of the Duke Farm in Orange County, N.C., ca. 1910-1919. (See also information folder with inventory.) Benjamin Newton Duke's Durham home "Four Acres" is represented by two sets of exterior and interior photographs, ca. 1910 and 1961.
The Richard B. Arrington Papers Series is composed of the personal papers of Benjamin Newton Duke's personal secretary and business agent, who worked in the New York office. This series is comprised of letters, letterbook, accounts, check stubs, and receipts. Correspondence covers two periods: 1903-1907 and 1911-1914. From 1903to 1907 the major focus is building and furnishing a house on Ridgeview Road in White Plains, N.Y. From 1911 the emphasis is on Mr. Arrington's business interests, including stock transactions and insurance. Since Richard Arrington died April 17, 1913, the remainder of the correspondence (1913-1914) concerns his estate. His wife, Ethel Lewis Arrington,carried on much of his personal business during this period. The accounts, check stubs and receipts pertain to Mr. Arrington's general business activities; the major focus is on stock transactions especially of the Piedmont Syndicate. Much of his business parallels his work for Benjamin Newton Duke.
The Alexander H. Sands, Jr., Papers Series contains personal papers belonging to another of Benjamin Newton Duke's secretary/agents in his New Yorkoffice. The series includes letters, letterbooks, account book, check registers, check stubs, a daybook, ledger and receipts. The correspondence, 1910-1918, primarily concerns Mr. Sands's family matters and personal business interests. He also supported both his parents, Mary Harvey Sands and Tucker K. Sands. Alexander H. Sands's business papers, like those of Richard Arrington, often parallel his work for Benjamin Newton Duke. In addition to detailing stock transactions and other business, these records include an account book of the Southern Audit Company of New York, Inc., for 1914-1915,of which Sands was a partner.
Of primary interest in the Miscellaneous Series is a diary, 1927-1929, of Sarah Pearson Angier Duke, including entries for Benjamin Newton Duke's lengthy illness and death. A folder on family genealogy includes notes on the baptisms of Benjamin and Sarah Duke'schildren. Other files pertain to the funerals of Benjamin Newtonand Sarah Pearson Angier Duke, memorials for Angier Buchanan Duke and James Buchanan Duke,and tributes to Benjamin Newton Duke made during his lifetime and after his death. The bulk of the Miscellaneous Series includes information on many of the businesses in which Mr. Duke had an interest. Examples include The American Tobacco Company; Dixie Fire Insurance Company;Great Falls Power Company; Jim Butler Tonopah Mining Company; Kansas City, Mexico and Orient Railway Company;and Seaboard Air Line Railway. General files will be found on banking, churches, cotton mills, mining, public utilities, and social welfare agencies. All of these businesses are well represented in both the Correspondence and the Financial Papers Series.
Related collections in the Rubenstein Library are the James Buchanan Duke Papers, the Washington Duke Papers, and the Semans Family Papers. In addition to correspondence, these collections contain many photographs of Duke family members. The Duke University Archives is another source of information on the relationship of the Duke family to Duke University.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Duke, Sarah Pearson Angier, 1856-1936
Trinity College (Durham, N.C.)
W. Duke, Sons and Company (Durham, N.C.)
American Tobacco Company
Erwin Mills (Durham, N.C)
Mayo Mills
Durham Electric Lighting Company
Spray Water Power and Land Company
Dallas Cable Railroad
Durham Fertilizer Company
Alaska Dredging and Power Company
Solomon River Hydraulic Mining Company
Governors -- North Carolina -- Election
Tobacco industry -- North Carolina
Electric utilities -- North Carolina
Universities and colleges -- North Carolina
North Carolina -- Industries
Banks and banking -- North Carolina
Duke, Benjamin Newton
Duke, Angier Buchanan, 1884-1923
Biddle, Mary Duke 1887-1960
Biddle, Anthony Joseph Drexel, 1896-1961
Arrington, Richard B., d. 1913
Sands, Alexander H. 1891-1960
Photographs
Contents of Collection
- Correspondence Series, 1871-1941, undated, (77 containers)
  Letters, letterbooks, receipts, bills, memoranda, telegrams, minutes, and printed reports related to the financial, philanthropic, and personal interests of Benjamin Newton Duke. Correspondence is arranged in two categories: letters and letterbooks. These are filed chronologically with letterbooks following letters. The fragile letterbooks (1892-1923) consist of bound carbon-copies of outgoing correspondence.
  - Letters
    - 1872-1891, (16 folders) (Box 1)
    - 1892, (14 folders) (Box 2)
    - 1893, Jan.-Sept., (14 folders) (Box 3)
    - 1893, Oct.-1894, July, (13 folders) (Box 4)
    - 1894, Aug.-1895, Mar., (16 folders) (Box 5)
    - 1895, Apr.-Nov., (16 folders) (Box 6)
    - 1895, Dec.-1896, May, (16 folders) (Box 7)
    - 1896, June-Dec., (16 folders) (Box 8)
    - 1897, Jan.-Sept., (19 folders) (Box 9)
    - 1897, Oct.-1898, May, (15 folders) (Box 10)
    - 1898, June-Dec., (17 folders) (Box 11)
    - 1899, Jan.-July, (15 folders) (Box 12)
    - 1899, Aug.-1900, Jan., (15 folders) (Box 13)
    - 1900, Feb.-Oct., (17 folders) (Box 14)
    - 1900, Nov.-1901, Apr., (15 folders) (Box 15)
    - 1901, May-Oct., (14 folders) (Box 16)
    - 1901, Nov.-1902, Mar., (17 folders) (Box 17)
    - 1902, Apr.-Aug., (16 folders) (Box 18)
    - 1902, Sept.-1902, Dec. 20, (12 folders) (Box 19)
    - 1903, Jan.-Apr., (12 folders) (Box 20)
    - 1903, May-Sept., (15 folders) (Box 21)
    - 1903, Oct.-1904, Mar., (16 folders) (Box 22)
    - 1904, Apr.-Sept., (16 folders) (Box 23)
    - 1904, Oct.-1905, Mar., (15 folders) (Box 24)
    - 1905, Apr.-Aug., (13 folders) (Box 25)
    - 1905, Sept.-Dec. and undated (Box 26)
    - 1906, Jan.-Apr., (17 folders) (Box 27)
    - 1906, May-Oct., (18 folders) (Box 28)
    - 1906, Nov.-1907, Mar., (17 folders) (Box 29)
    - 1907, Apr.-Sept., (17 folders) (Box 30)
    - 1907, Oct.-1908, Feb., (17 folders) (Box 31)
    - 1908, Mar.-June, (14 folders) (Box 32)
    - 1908, July-1908, Oct., (14 folders) (Box 33)
    - 1908, Nov.-1909, Feb., (14 folders) (Box 34)
    - 1909, Mar.-July, (17 folders) (Box 35)
    - 1909, Aug.-Nov., (16 folders) (Box 36)
    - 1909, Dec.-1910, Mar., (17 folders) (Box 37)
    - 1910, Apr.-1910, June, (12 folders) (Box 38)
    - 1910, July-Sept., (15 folders) (Box 39)
    - 1910, Oct.-Dec. and undated, (18 folders) (Box 40)
    - 1911, Jan.-Mar., (16 folders) (Box 41)
    - 1911, Apr.-June, (14 folders) (Box 42)
    - 1911, July-Nov., (14 folders) (Box 43)
    - 1911, Dec.-1912, Jan., (12 folders) (Box 44)
    - 1912, Feb.-Apr., (14 folders) (Box 45)
    - 1912, May-July, (12 folders) (Box 46)
    - 1912, Aug.-Nov., (15 folders) (Box 47)
    - 1912, Dec.-1913, Feb., (13 folders) (Box 48)
    - 1913, Mar.-Apr., (10 folders) (Box 49)
    - 1913, May-July, (15 folders) (Box 50)
    - 1913, Aug.-Oct., (14 folders) (Box 51)
    - 1913, Nov.-1914, Jan., (13 folders) (Box 52)
    - 1914, Feb.-Apr., (14 folders) (Box 53)
    - 1914, May-July, (14 folders) (Box 54)
    - 1914, Aug.-Oct., (13 folders) (Box 55)
    - 1914, Nov.-1915, Jan., (14 folders) (Box 56)
    - 1915, Feb.-Apr., (12 folders) (Box 57)
    - 1915, May-Aug., (13 folders) (Box 58)
    - 1915, Sept.-Dec. and undated, (15 folders) (Box 59)
    - 1916, Jan.-May, (21 folders) (Box 60)
    - 1918, June-1923, Dec., (20 folders) (Box 61)
    - 1924, Jan.-1928, Dec., (13 folders) (Box 62)
    - 1929-1941, undated, (6 folders) (Box 63)
    - Condolences, 1923-1924: Angier B. Duke, A-Z, (2 folders)
  - Letterbooks
    - 1892, Apr. 7-1894, Aug. 29 (3 vols.) (Box 64)
    - 1894, Aug. 29-1895, Nov. 11 (2 vols.) (Box 65)
    - 1895, Nov. 11-1897, May 7 (3 vols.) (Box 66)
    - 1897, May 8-1901, Mar. 18 (3 vols.) (Box 67)
    - 1901, Mar. 19-1910, May 6 (3 vols.) (Box 68)
    - 1910, May 9-1911, May 17 (3 vols.) (Box 69)
    - 1911, May 18-1912, July 15 (2 vols.) (Box 70)
    - 1912, July 16-1913, Sept. 20 (2 vols.) (Box 71)
    - 1913, Sept. 17-1915, Apr. 8 (2 vols.) (Box 72)
    - 1915, Apr. 12-1916, Sept. 18 (2 vols.) (Box 73)
    - 916, Sept. 18-1917, Sept. 11 (2 vols.) (Box 74)
    - 1917, Sept. 12-1918, Apr. 25 (1 vol.) (Box 75)
    - 1911, Mar. 17-1923, Apr. 21 (3 vols.) (Box 76)
- Financial Papers, 1884-1924, undated, (46 containers)
  Reflects the scope of the personal, business and philanthropic interests of Benjamin Newton Duke. Types of records from Mr. Duke's Durham and New York offices include bills, charitable contributions, check stubs, invoices, statements of accounts, tax statements, minutes, receipts, stock transactions, trial balances, household and petty cash accounts. Bills and receipts are arranged chronologically at the beginning of the series. The remaining papers are arranged alphabetically by topic or type of record.
  - 1884-1899, Aug., (17 folders) (Box 77)
  - 1899, Sept.-1900, Aug., (13 folders) (Box 78)
  - 1900, Sept.-1901, May, (16 folders) (Box 79)
  - 1901, June-1902, Mar., (17 folders) (Box 80)
  - 1902, Apr.-1902, Nov., (16 folders) (Box 81)
  - 1902, Dec.-1904, Apr., (17 folders) (Box 82)
  - 1904, May-1905, Sept., (15 folders) (Box 83)
  - 1905, Oct.-1906, July, (14 folders) (Box 84)
  - 1906, Aug.-1907, May, (14 folders) (Box 85)
  - 1907, June -1908, Apr., (12 folders) (Box 86)
  - 1908, May-Dec., (15 folders) (Box 87)
  - 1909, Jan.-July, (13 folders) (Box 88)
  - 1909, Aug.-1910, Jan., (14 folders) (Box 89)
  - 1910, Feb.-June, (10 folders) (Box 90)
  - 1910, July-Nov., (10 folders) (Box 91)
  - 1910, Dec.-1911, Apr., (13 folders) (Box 92)
  - 1911, May-Oct., (12 folders) (Box 93)
  - 1911, Nov.-1912, Feb., (10 folders) (Box 94)
  - 1912, Mar.-June, (8 folders) (Box 95)
  - 1912, July-Oct., (8 folders) (Box 96)
  - 1912, Nov.-1913, Feb., (10 folders) (Box 97)
  - 1913, Mar.-May, (8 folders) (Box 98)
  - 1913, June-Aug., (9 folders) (Box 99)
  - 1913, Sept.-Nov., (9 folders) (Box 100)
  - 1913, Dec.-1914, Mar., (11 folders) (Box 101)
  - 1914, Apr.-June, (9 folders) (Box 102)
  - 1914, July-Oct., (9 folders) (Box 103)
  - 1914, Nov.-1915, Feb., (10 folders) (Box 104)
  - 1915, Mar.-July, (10 folders) (Box 105)
  - 1915, Aug.-1916, Jan., (12 folders) (Box 106)
  - 1916, Feb.-Dec., (12 folders) (Box 107)
  - 1917, Jan.-Dec., (13 folders) (Box 108)
  - 1918, Jan.-1919, Dec., (12 folders) (Box 109)
  - 1920, Jan.-1924, undated, (13 folders) (Box 110)
  - Accounts: (Box 111)
    - William H. Butler--; Tobacco Stemmer Stock, ca. 1913
    - Benjamin Newton Duke with:
      - Alfred de Cordova & Co., ca. 1898-1911
      - Daniel O'Dell & Co., 1912-1913
      - The Farmers' Loan & Trust Co., 1891-1892
      - Fellowes, Davis & Co., 1898-1899
      - Halsted & Harrison, 1907-1917
      - Moore & Schley, 1912-1913
      - Newburger, Henderson & Loeb, 1908, 1913
      - Raymond, Pynchon & Co., 1913, Feb.-June
    - Brodie L. Duke-- Tobacco Purchases, 1876, Oct.-1878, Jan.
    - James B. Duke with:
      - Banks and Trust Companies., 1913
      - Southern Power Co., 1913
    - Sarah Pearson Angier Duke with:
      - Benjamin Newton Duke, 1916-1917
      - The Fidelity Bank, 1916-1922, undated, (3 folders)
      - Guaranty Trust Co. of New York, 1916-1922
  - Assets/Liabilities: Benjamin N. Duke, ca. 1913 (Box 112)
  - Cash Statements:
    - James B. Duke:; Southern Power Co., 1913, June-Sept.
    - Benjamin N. Duke and family, 1917, Jan.-May
  - Charitable Contributions: 1892-1928, undated (typescript lists)
  - Gifts to family members: (Roney-Duke families), 1925-1927